<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Vietnam Overview &#8211; Travel News</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/webtravelnews/category/vietnam-overview/feed/?simply_static_page=8677" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:50:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Overseas Monuments Commemorating President Ho Chi Minh (Part 1)</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/overseas-monuments-commemorating-president-ho-chi-minh-part-1/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/overseas-monuments-commemorating-president-ho-chi-minh-part-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam Overview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=57</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A lot of countries in the world in Asia, Europe, Africa, and America erected statues of President Ho Chi Minh to commemorate a world cultural celebrity. Now, we introduce meaningful stops in abroad in occasion of celebrating the 124th birthday of Vietnam’s late president Ho Chi Minh. China At house number 248 and 250 (no.13 [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A lot of countries in the world in Asia, Europe, Africa, and America erected statues of President Ho Chi Minh to commemorate a world cultural celebrity.</p>



<p>Now, we introduce meaningful stops in abroad in occasion of celebrating the 124th birthday of Vietnam’s late president Ho Chi Minh.</p>



<p><strong>China</strong></p>



<p>At house number 248 and 250 (no.13 and 13/1 in the past), Van Minh street, Quang Chau city, Quang Dong province is a place where first party members – a core class of party members were directly trained by President Ho Chi Minh.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/long-chau.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/long-chau.jpg" alt="long chau" class="wp-image-374"/></a></figure>



<p>Monuments of president Ho Chi Minh at Lieu Chau, Quang Tay include the detention cave for Ho Chi Minh, Nam Duong hostel after the president was set free (1943-1944), Lac Quan hotel was a place where Vietnam party leaders worked, the house number 1 in Hong Lau was a meeting place where president Ho Chi Minh talked to president Chu An Lai.</p>



<p>Memorial house of president Ho Chi Minh in North street, Long Chau district, Quang Tay province displays and preserves images, documents and exhibits of president Ho Chi Minh and Vietnam party member during 18 year communist activities.</p>



<p>The office Bat lo quan in Trung Son Bac street, Que Lam city, Quang Tay province is a place where president Ho Chi Minh usually read book or contacted to other communists and now the office shows images and exhibits of Vietnam communist leaders.</p>



<p><strong>Thailand</strong></p>



<p>Monuments of president Ho Chi Minh in May village, Muong district, Nakhon Phanom province is a place where tourists and overseas Vietnamese in Thailand burn incense to commemorate the president in occasion of ceremonies, New year, especially birthday and death ceremony. They also come to know more about the life and career of the president, particularly in his working time in Thailand from 1928 to 1929.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/thai-lan.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/thai-lan.jpg" alt="thai lan" class="wp-image-375"/></a></figure>



<p><em>Tourists in Monuments of President Ho in Thailand</em></p>



<p>Monuments of president Ho Chi Minh in Noong On village, Xieng Phin commune, Muong district, Udon Thani province- where the president had stayed and had worked since 1928 under name Thầu Chín.</p>



<p><strong>Laos</strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/Lao-2.bmp"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/Lao-2.bmp" alt="Lao 2" class="wp-image-376"/></a></figure>



<p>Monuments of president Ho Chi Minh in Xieng Vang village, Noong Boc district, Kham Muon province was inaugurated and opened for public on May 19, 2012 on the occasion of celebrating the 122 birthday of the People.</p>



<p><strong>Singapore</strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/singapore.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/singapore.jpg" alt="singapore" class="wp-image-377"/></a></figure>



<p>Memorial stele and statue of president Ho Chi Minh at Asian Civilizations Museum, near Singapore river. The memorial stele was opened for public use on May, 2008 on the occasion of 118<sup>th</sup>&nbsp;birthday of president Ho Chi Minh and 35- year bilateral relations between Vietnam and Singapore. The statue of president Ho Chi Minh is the first one in the honor program “Friends have come our country” of Singapore. The statue was inaugurated in 2011.</p>



<p><strong>The Philippines</strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/philippine.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/philippine.jpg" alt="philippine" class="wp-image-378"/></a></figure>



<p>The statue of president Ho Chi Minh at Laguna State Polytechnic College, Manila was inaugurated on May 19, 2010 on the occasion of the president’s 120<sup>th</sup>&nbsp;birthday.</p>



<p>The statue of president Ho Chi Minh at ASEAN Park, Manila was opened for public use in 2011 to commemorate 35- year bilateral relations between the Philippines and Vietnam.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/overseas-monuments-commemorating-president-ho-chi-minh-part-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hoi An Urban (World Cultural Heritage)</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/hoi-an-urban-world-cultural-heritage/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/hoi-an-urban-world-cultural-heritage/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam Overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vietnam World Heritages]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=54</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hoi An is an ancient town of Vietnam, located downstream of the confluence of Thu Bon river (coastal plain of Quang Nam province), 30 km from Da Nang city to the south. Hoi An used to be known on the international market with many different names such as Lam Ap, Faifo, Hoai Pho and Hoi [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-1.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-1.jpg" alt="post 1" class="wp-image-402"/></a></figure>



<p>Hoi An is an ancient town of Vietnam, located downstream of the confluence of Thu Bon river (coastal plain of Quang Nam province), 30 km from Da Nang city to the south. Hoi An used to be known on the international market with many different names such as Lam Ap, Faifo, Hoai Pho and Hoi An.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-2.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-2.jpg" alt="post 2" class="wp-image-403"/></a></figure>



<p>As a unique traditional Southeast Asian port style in Vietnam and rare in the world, Hoi An almost keep over a thousand architectural monuments such as streets, buildings, halls, temples, pagodas , temples, family temples, ancient wells, ancient tombs, etc. The architectures just have Vietnamese traditional art, just express the integration of cultural exchanges with Eastern and Western countries. Over centuries, customs, ceremonies, cultural and religious activities as well as traditional foods are still preserved by many generations of the ancient town. Hoi An has a healthy natural environment, a quiet suburb with lovely small villages with crafts such as carpentry, bronze making, ceramic, etc.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-3.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-3.jpg" alt="post 3" class="wp-image-404"/></a></figure>



<p>Researchers suggest that the ancient architecture of Hoi An is almost restored since the early 19th century, although it may be constructed much earlier. Ancient architecture is most evident in the Old Quarter Hoi An. Totally located in Minh An ward with total area of 2 square kilometers, focuses most famous relics in Hoi An. The streets in the old town are short and narrow; some curved, and run along as checkerboard style. The topography of the ancient town tilts gradually from north to south. Most architectural works of the old town were built with traditional materials: brick and wood. Visitors easily recognize old ages in every architectural style of works everywhere: on yin-yang roof tiles covered moss and grass; gray moldy walls, old; the carving of a strange animal, or describing a tale, etc.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-4.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-4.jpg" alt="post 4" class="wp-image-405"/></a></figure>



<p>The cultural richness and diversity in mind of Hoi An people are also manifested in the traditional dishes like Cao Lau, Wonton, etc. which has long been preserved. The life has changed from year after year but Hoianians have not lost familiar songs and cultural festivals. They all are respectfully preserved.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-5.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-5.jpg" alt="post 5" class="wp-image-406"/></a></figure>



<p>At the 23<sup>rd</sup>&nbsp;session from November 29 to December 4, 1999 in Marrakesh (Morocco), Organization of Culture- Science – United Nations Education (UNESCO) recognized Hoi An in &nbsp;the list of World Cultural Heritage.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-9.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-9.jpg" alt="post 9" class="wp-image-410"/></a></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-8.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-8.jpg" alt="post 8" class="wp-image-409"/></a></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-7.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-7.jpg" alt="post 7" class="wp-image-408"/></a></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-6.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-6.jpg" alt="post 6" class="wp-image-407"/></a></figure>



<p>Vietnam warmly welcomes you to enjoy Vietnamese cuisine and to make your trip in smooth water, turn your plan into real by quick hands to obtain&nbsp;<strong>Vietnam visa</strong>&nbsp;at&nbsp;<a href="http://govietnamvisa.com/">http://govietnamvisa.com/</a>&nbsp;and for&nbsp;<strong>Vietnam eTicket</strong>&nbsp;at&nbsp;<a href="http://vietnamairlines247.com/">http://vietnamairlines247.com/</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/hoi-an-urban-world-cultural-heritage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Da Lat, the city where time slows down</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/da-lat-the-city-where-time-slows-down/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/da-lat-the-city-where-time-slows-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam Overview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=22</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Belonging to Lam Dong, a province of Central Highland of Vietnam, Da Lat is a small city at the altitude of 1500 meters which grants the city lovely climate that not many places in Vietnam have. With many beautiful landscapes and nice weather, Da Lat makes its way to the top destination in Vietnam and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Belonging to Lam Dong, a province of Central Highland of Vietnam, Da Lat is a small city at the altitude of 1500 meters which grants the city lovely climate that not many places in Vietnam have.</p>



<p>With many beautiful landscapes and nice weather, Da Lat makes its way to the top destination in Vietnam and its journey to higher rank in the list seems not to stop.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="700" height="400" src="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/con-duong-da-lat-a4.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-26" srcset="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/con-duong-da-lat-a4.jpg 700w, https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/con-duong-da-lat-a4-300x171.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Da Lat the foggy city</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>Thanks to its natural advantages, Da Lat is home to thousands of flower pieces, which make the city literally sank in the flower colors all year round and also the reason the city is dubbed as the city of thousands flowers, the love city or the foggy city. Granted with lovely weather that is lightly cold at night and foggy in the early morning, pine forests hugging the city, Da Lat looks definitely romantic and poetic. An as a beloved child of the God, this place has zero storm, only strong winds can reach it.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide size-full"><img decoding="async" width="700" height="500" src="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/1554722331_du-lich-da-lat-ngam-hoa-3.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-27" srcset="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/1554722331_du-lich-da-lat-ngam-hoa-3.jpg 700w, https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/1554722331_du-lich-da-lat-ngam-hoa-3-300x214.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>The stunning road of cherry blossom in Da Lat</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The first special thing that tourists to Da Lat may notice is that the city has no traffic light. It does make sense if we take a look at the geographic conditions of the city. It’s located on a plateau with many slopes so no one here ever wants to drive fast. Also, the population density in Da Lat is not high so the number of vehicles is low, roads here are quite open.&nbsp;Secondly visitors also may notice is that it’s hard to find an AC here in Da Lat and it’s totally easy to understand as it is cool all year round.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide size-full"><img decoding="async" width="1000" height="667" src="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/phuong-tim-11.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-35" srcset="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/phuong-tim-11.jpg 1000w, https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/phuong-tim-11-300x200.jpg 300w, https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/phuong-tim-11-768x512.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Da Lat can lack anything but flowers</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>Beside, the most obvious thing that could be sensed here in Da Lat is the peace. Unlike other cities in Vietnam, this city preserves its peaceful atmosphere quite well so visitors hardly could find a hustle and bustle city here but a dreamy city in quiet. The life beat here is quite slow, it could even affect visitors. Walking slowly in the foliage of the flower city, you may suddenly find yourself&nbsp;live, think more slowly when you’re out there in the world, even your heart beats more slowly.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/da-lat-the-city-where-time-slows-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
