<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Travel News</title>
	<atom:link href="http://localhost/webtravelnews/feed/?simply_static_page=8650" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:50:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Mother Goddess worship-the local religion of Vietnam</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-culture/mother-goddess-worship-the-local-religion-of-vietnam/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-culture/mother-goddess-worship-the-local-religion-of-vietnam/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=60</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Among intangilble cultural heritages recognized by UNESCO in Vietnam, Dao Mau or Morther Goddess worship receives the least attention from foreign visitors. However, it has been an important part in religious life of a part Vietnamese.&#160;For several centuries in Vietnam, the religion has been a source of strength, inspiration and spirituality — particularly among working-class [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Among intangilble cultural heritages recognized by UNESCO in Vietnam, Dao Mau or Morther Goddess worship receives the least attention from foreign visitors. However, it has been an important part in religious life of a part Vietnamese.&nbsp;For several centuries in Vietnam, the religion has been a source of strength, inspiration and spirituality — particularly among working-class families.<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/tam-toa-thanh-mau.jpg"></a></p>



<p>The tradition of the religion is to worship Goddesses, some of them were born in legends by mouth and some deified from real historic individuals. This is a local religion inspired by the Dao religious, it takes the female with the natural ability of offspring and protect children as a Goddess. By worshipping Goddess inspired by the image of the Mother, the religion reflects the desire to escape from the rope and prejudice of feudal society prior to male.</p>



<p>Initially, devoted to female deities, Mother Goddess worship was established in the 16th century as an alternative to Confucianism as women were expected to play a passive, submissive and subservient role. They were not well respected and had to rely on men. The people needed a symbol, so they invented mother goddess Lieu Hanh, who representing&nbsp;Vietnamese women’s burning desire for freedom, independence and happiness.<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/mau-lieu-hanh.jpg"></a></p>



<p>In Mother Goddess worship,&nbsp;Hau Dong&nbsp;(loosely means ‘to mount the medium’ or ‘to go into a trance’) is the most important step.&nbsp;During the ceremony, mediums (who are traditionally chosen by deities at birth) and their assistants will don bright costumes, make offerings to Buddha, perform folk dances and petition the goddesses to descend and possess their bodies.&nbsp;When spirits are believed to have entered the body, the medium will appear to change personalities. From that point onward, all actions and words are said to be those of the spirit.</p>



<p>This is believed that these spirits will bless the mediums with health, hope, happiness and good luck.&nbsp;When the fragrance of the joss sticks and the music combined they would have the chance to ask god them. The dance is quite different from normal acting in life.&nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/sss-1-590x308.jpg"></a></p>



<p>In the past, there used to be a period of time the religion nearly came to an end but luckily it was still preserved and time flies, together with the development of economy, the demand for religious life goes up and Mother Goddess worship has revived and become an indispensable part in the life of Vietnamese people.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-culture/mother-goddess-worship-the-local-religion-of-vietnam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Overseas Monuments Commemorating President Ho Chi Minh (Part 1)</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/overseas-monuments-commemorating-president-ho-chi-minh-part-1/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/overseas-monuments-commemorating-president-ho-chi-minh-part-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam Overview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=57</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A lot of countries in the world in Asia, Europe, Africa, and America erected statues of President Ho Chi Minh to commemorate a world cultural celebrity. Now, we introduce meaningful stops in abroad in occasion of celebrating the 124th birthday of Vietnam’s late president Ho Chi Minh. China At house number 248 and 250 (no.13 [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A lot of countries in the world in Asia, Europe, Africa, and America erected statues of President Ho Chi Minh to commemorate a world cultural celebrity.</p>



<p>Now, we introduce meaningful stops in abroad in occasion of celebrating the 124th birthday of Vietnam’s late president Ho Chi Minh.</p>



<p><strong>China</strong></p>



<p>At house number 248 and 250 (no.13 and 13/1 in the past), Van Minh street, Quang Chau city, Quang Dong province is a place where first party members – a core class of party members were directly trained by President Ho Chi Minh.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/long-chau.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/long-chau.jpg" alt="long chau" class="wp-image-374"/></a></figure>



<p>Monuments of president Ho Chi Minh at Lieu Chau, Quang Tay include the detention cave for Ho Chi Minh, Nam Duong hostel after the president was set free (1943-1944), Lac Quan hotel was a place where Vietnam party leaders worked, the house number 1 in Hong Lau was a meeting place where president Ho Chi Minh talked to president Chu An Lai.</p>



<p>Memorial house of president Ho Chi Minh in North street, Long Chau district, Quang Tay province displays and preserves images, documents and exhibits of president Ho Chi Minh and Vietnam party member during 18 year communist activities.</p>



<p>The office Bat lo quan in Trung Son Bac street, Que Lam city, Quang Tay province is a place where president Ho Chi Minh usually read book or contacted to other communists and now the office shows images and exhibits of Vietnam communist leaders.</p>



<p><strong>Thailand</strong></p>



<p>Monuments of president Ho Chi Minh in May village, Muong district, Nakhon Phanom province is a place where tourists and overseas Vietnamese in Thailand burn incense to commemorate the president in occasion of ceremonies, New year, especially birthday and death ceremony. They also come to know more about the life and career of the president, particularly in his working time in Thailand from 1928 to 1929.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/thai-lan.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/thai-lan.jpg" alt="thai lan" class="wp-image-375"/></a></figure>



<p><em>Tourists in Monuments of President Ho in Thailand</em></p>



<p>Monuments of president Ho Chi Minh in Noong On village, Xieng Phin commune, Muong district, Udon Thani province- where the president had stayed and had worked since 1928 under name Thầu Chín.</p>



<p><strong>Laos</strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/Lao-2.bmp"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/Lao-2.bmp" alt="Lao 2" class="wp-image-376"/></a></figure>



<p>Monuments of president Ho Chi Minh in Xieng Vang village, Noong Boc district, Kham Muon province was inaugurated and opened for public on May 19, 2012 on the occasion of celebrating the 122 birthday of the People.</p>



<p><strong>Singapore</strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/singapore.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/singapore.jpg" alt="singapore" class="wp-image-377"/></a></figure>



<p>Memorial stele and statue of president Ho Chi Minh at Asian Civilizations Museum, near Singapore river. The memorial stele was opened for public use on May, 2008 on the occasion of 118<sup>th</sup>&nbsp;birthday of president Ho Chi Minh and 35- year bilateral relations between Vietnam and Singapore. The statue of president Ho Chi Minh is the first one in the honor program “Friends have come our country” of Singapore. The statue was inaugurated in 2011.</p>



<p><strong>The Philippines</strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/philippine.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/06/philippine.jpg" alt="philippine" class="wp-image-378"/></a></figure>



<p>The statue of president Ho Chi Minh at Laguna State Polytechnic College, Manila was inaugurated on May 19, 2010 on the occasion of the president’s 120<sup>th</sup>&nbsp;birthday.</p>



<p>The statue of president Ho Chi Minh at ASEAN Park, Manila was opened for public use in 2011 to commemorate 35- year bilateral relations between the Philippines and Vietnam.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/overseas-monuments-commemorating-president-ho-chi-minh-part-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hoi An Urban (World Cultural Heritage)</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/hoi-an-urban-world-cultural-heritage/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/hoi-an-urban-world-cultural-heritage/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam Overview]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vietnam World Heritages]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=54</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hoi An is an ancient town of Vietnam, located downstream of the confluence of Thu Bon river (coastal plain of Quang Nam province), 30 km from Da Nang city to the south. Hoi An used to be known on the international market with many different names such as Lam Ap, Faifo, Hoai Pho and Hoi [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-1.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-1.jpg" alt="post 1" class="wp-image-402"/></a></figure>



<p>Hoi An is an ancient town of Vietnam, located downstream of the confluence of Thu Bon river (coastal plain of Quang Nam province), 30 km from Da Nang city to the south. Hoi An used to be known on the international market with many different names such as Lam Ap, Faifo, Hoai Pho and Hoi An.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-2.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-2.jpg" alt="post 2" class="wp-image-403"/></a></figure>



<p>As a unique traditional Southeast Asian port style in Vietnam and rare in the world, Hoi An almost keep over a thousand architectural monuments such as streets, buildings, halls, temples, pagodas , temples, family temples, ancient wells, ancient tombs, etc. The architectures just have Vietnamese traditional art, just express the integration of cultural exchanges with Eastern and Western countries. Over centuries, customs, ceremonies, cultural and religious activities as well as traditional foods are still preserved by many generations of the ancient town. Hoi An has a healthy natural environment, a quiet suburb with lovely small villages with crafts such as carpentry, bronze making, ceramic, etc.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-3.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-3.jpg" alt="post 3" class="wp-image-404"/></a></figure>



<p>Researchers suggest that the ancient architecture of Hoi An is almost restored since the early 19th century, although it may be constructed much earlier. Ancient architecture is most evident in the Old Quarter Hoi An. Totally located in Minh An ward with total area of 2 square kilometers, focuses most famous relics in Hoi An. The streets in the old town are short and narrow; some curved, and run along as checkerboard style. The topography of the ancient town tilts gradually from north to south. Most architectural works of the old town were built with traditional materials: brick and wood. Visitors easily recognize old ages in every architectural style of works everywhere: on yin-yang roof tiles covered moss and grass; gray moldy walls, old; the carving of a strange animal, or describing a tale, etc.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-4.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-4.jpg" alt="post 4" class="wp-image-405"/></a></figure>



<p>The cultural richness and diversity in mind of Hoi An people are also manifested in the traditional dishes like Cao Lau, Wonton, etc. which has long been preserved. The life has changed from year after year but Hoianians have not lost familiar songs and cultural festivals. They all are respectfully preserved.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-5.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-5.jpg" alt="post 5" class="wp-image-406"/></a></figure>



<p>At the 23<sup>rd</sup>&nbsp;session from November 29 to December 4, 1999 in Marrakesh (Morocco), Organization of Culture- Science – United Nations Education (UNESCO) recognized Hoi An in &nbsp;the list of World Cultural Heritage.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-9.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-9.jpg" alt="post 9" class="wp-image-410"/></a></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-8.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-8.jpg" alt="post 8" class="wp-image-409"/></a></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-7.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-7.jpg" alt="post 7" class="wp-image-408"/></a></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-6.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/post-6.jpg" alt="post 6" class="wp-image-407"/></a></figure>



<p>Vietnam warmly welcomes you to enjoy Vietnamese cuisine and to make your trip in smooth water, turn your plan into real by quick hands to obtain&nbsp;<strong>Vietnam visa</strong>&nbsp;at&nbsp;<a href="http://govietnamvisa.com/">http://govietnamvisa.com/</a>&nbsp;and for&nbsp;<strong>Vietnam eTicket</strong>&nbsp;at&nbsp;<a href="http://vietnamairlines247.com/">http://vietnamairlines247.com/</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/hoi-an-urban-world-cultural-heritage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hung Kings Temple Festival – Intangible Cultural Heritage of Humanity</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-world-heritages/hung-kings-temple-festival-intangible-cultural-heritage-of-humanity/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-world-heritages/hung-kings-temple-festival-intangible-cultural-heritage-of-humanity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam World Heritages]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=51</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hung Kings Temple Festival (Gio to Hung Vuong) is&#160;one of the most important national&#160;holidays in&#160;Vietnam&#160;to commemorate Hung Kings who had built the country at its early stage.&#160;The festival strengthens the importance of a long-standing philosophy in Vietnamese culture: “when you drink water, remember the source” (Uong nuoc nho nguon). Annually, the&#160;festival begins with a lot [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Hung Kings Temple Festival (<em>Gio to Hung Vuong</em>) is&nbsp;one of the most important national&nbsp;holidays in&nbsp;Vietnam&nbsp;to commemorate Hung Kings who had built the country at its early stage.&nbsp;The festival strengthens the importance of a long-standing philosophy in Vietnamese culture: “when you drink water, remember the source” (<strong><em>Uong nuoc nho nguon</em></strong>).</p>



<p>Annually, the&nbsp;festival begins with a lot of cultural activities in several days before a main ceremony held&nbsp;on the&nbsp;<strong>10th day of the third lunar month</strong>&nbsp;at Hung Temple, Nghia Linh Moutain,&nbsp;<strong>Phu Tho Province</strong>&nbsp;(North of Vietnam). With its special values, the worship of Hung Kings in Phu Tho was officially recognized by the UNESCO as one of the&nbsp;<strong>Intangible Cultural Heritages of Humanity</strong>&nbsp;on December 6<sup>th</sup>, 2012.</p>



<p>Hung Kings Temple Festival is divided into two main parts:&nbsp;<strong>ceremony</strong>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<strong>cultural activities</strong>.&nbsp;The ceremony is&nbsp;honorably held&nbsp;at&nbsp;the Upper Temple (<em>Den Thuong</em>) which is in the top of the mountain. After the ceremony, cultural activities are held&nbsp;around the mountain foot&nbsp;with the participation of surrounding villages.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>1.&nbsp;The ceremony:</strong></h2>



<p>The ceremony is solemnly held with the presence of government leaders, village elders, villagers and tourists. The procession is led by a glorious palanquin with offerings consisting of “<em>Le tam sinh</em>” (a pig, a goat, and a cow),&nbsp;<em>Banh chung</em>&nbsp;(square glutinous rice cake),&nbsp;<em>Banh day</em>&nbsp;(round glutinous rice cake) and colorful sticky rice. The “<em>Senh tien</em>” traditional dance of&nbsp;<em>Mong</em>&nbsp;people is also a special part of the festival.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/Banh-Chung.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/Banh-Chung.jpg" alt="Banh-Chung" class="wp-image-2332"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Banh chung (Photo: Internet)</em></figcaption></figure>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/cach-lam-banh-giay-dau-xanh-101.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/cach-lam-banh-giay-dau-xanh-101.jpg" alt="cach-lam-banh-giay-dau-xanh-101" class="wp-image-2333"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Banh day&nbsp;(Photo: Internet)</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>In the early morning of 10<sup>th</sup>&nbsp;March, incense-offering ritual is carried out by leaders of the nation, representatives of Phu Tho province as well as representatives of other provinces. Next is the turn of village elders and finally other people.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/ctn_dang_huong_tuong_niem_cac_vua_hung_tai_khu_di_tich_lich_su_den_hung.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/ctn_dang_huong_tuong_niem_cac_vua_hung_tai_khu_di_tich_lich_su_den_hung.jpg" alt="ctn_dang_huong_tuong_niem_cac_vua_hung_tai_khu_di_tich_lich_su_den_hung" class="wp-image-2334"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>The governments in Hung Kings Festival (Photo: Internet)</em></figcaption></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>2.&nbsp;The&nbsp;cultural&nbsp;activities:</strong></h2>



<p>A&nbsp;huge procession starts at the foot of the mountain, consisting of pilgrims, xoan classical song performances, and ca tru classical operas at several temples along the way towards the main Hung Temple.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>*Palanquin competition:</strong></h3>



<p>Lavish palanquins in the competition with the participation of surrounding villages creates convivial atmosphere for the festival.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/best_bf107e2808-1-lehoi-1-.jpeg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/best_bf107e2808-1-lehoi-1-.jpeg" alt="best_bf107e2808-1-lehoi 1-" class="wp-image-2335"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Procession to the Upper Temple for the solemn ceremony (Photo:&nbsp;Internet)</em></figcaption></figure>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>*Hat Xoan (Xoan Singing)</strong>:</h3>



<p><em>Hat Xoan</em>&nbsp;is one of the most unique and important rituals in the Hung Kings Temple Festival. Legend has it that&nbsp;<em>Hat Xoan</em>&nbsp;has been handed down from generation to generation since the time of Hung Kings.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/hat-xoan-phu-tho-truyen-thuyet-va-lich-su-share-636287288078917007.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/hat-xoan-phu-tho-truyen-thuyet-va-lich-su-share-636287288078917007.jpg" alt="hat-xoan-phu-tho-truyen-thuyet-va-lich-su-share-636287288078917007" class="wp-image-2336"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Hat Xoan (Photo:&nbsp;Internet)</em></figcaption></figure>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>*Other activities:</strong></h3>



<p>–&nbsp;Folk games:&nbsp;wrestling,&nbsp;<em>nem con</em>&nbsp;(throwing a colorful ball through a circle on the top of a high bamboo tree),&nbsp;<em>du tien</em>&nbsp;(swing a high bamboo swing), and cockfighting.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/hoi-nem-con.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/hoi-nem-con.jpg" alt="hoi-nem-con" class="wp-image-2337"/></a></figure>



<p>–&nbsp;Singing: There is&nbsp;a large stage for folk professional singers to perform traditional arts like&nbsp;<em>Cheo, Quan ho</em>,&nbsp;<em>Hat giao duyen</em>, and&nbsp;<em>Hat trong quan</em>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/quan-ho-singing.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/quan-ho-singing.jpg" alt="quan-ho-singing" class="wp-image-2338"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Quan ho singing&nbsp;(Photo:&nbsp;Internet)</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>–&nbsp;Competitions:&nbsp;“<em>Blowing fire to cook rice</em>”&nbsp;(Thoi lua nau com),&nbsp;“<em>making&nbsp;Banh Chung</em>” (Goi banh chung) and&nbsp;<em>Hat Xoan</em>&nbsp;competitions.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/btbd01-0134.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/btbd01-0134.jpg" alt="btbd01-0134" class="wp-image-2339"/></a></figure>



<p>In conclusion, the Hung Kings Temple Festival has played a crucial part in the spiritual lives of Vietnamese people. The worship rituals of the Hung Kings are closely related to the ancestral worship traditions of most Vietnamese families.&nbsp;It demonstrates a strong desire for national prosperity and symbolises community spirit. Coming to the festival is a deeply rooted custom in the minds of Vietnamese people in and outside the country.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-world-heritages/hung-kings-temple-festival-intangible-cultural-heritage-of-humanity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The imperial city of Hue-5 places cannot be missed</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-world-heritages/the-imperial-city-of-hue-5-places-cannot-be-missed/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-world-heritages/the-imperial-city-of-hue-5-places-cannot-be-missed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam World Heritages]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=48</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The imperial Hue is a large space, the most important place of the Nguyen Dynasty. Until now the place still preserves ancient cultures with palaces and temples. People put the first brick for Hue Imperial in 1805 when King Gia Long was reigning the country. It took 30 years to finish the structure. The structure [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The imperial Hue is a large space, the most important place of the Nguyen Dynasty. Until now the place still preserves ancient cultures with palaces and temples.</p>



<p>People put the first brick for Hue Imperial in 1805 when King Gia Long was reigning the country. It took 30 years to finish the structure. The structure is closed to a square with a length of 2.5km, the front side goes along the Huong river. Inside the structure, there is a smaller part called the Forbidden palace where the most important buildings of the Dynasty were located.<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/32580840706_0c40e6666b_b.jpg"></a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" src="http://localhost:8080/travelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/32580840706_0c40e6666b_b.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-53"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Hue Imperial city</em></figcaption></figure>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>1.Meridian Gate– The highlight</strong></h3>



<p>The meridian gate located at the south of the structure is the main entrance to Hue Imperial. It’s a complex architecture. It has the outlook of a magnificent castle but is still in harmony with natural scenes. From the gate, stairs made of long stone slabs lead to Five-Phoenix Pavillion.</p>



<p>The Pavillion is an open space where is always cool and windy. Standing at the Pavillion we can see all the Imperial.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/8e52e34b264d06d816a545dadf4dba3e.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/8e52e34b264d06d816a545dadf4dba3e.jpg" alt="8e52e34b264d06d816a545dadf4dba3e" class="wp-image-3527"/></a></figure>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>2. Thái Hòa palace –the symbol of the Nguyen Dynasty’s power</strong></h3>



<p>Thai Hoa Palace is located in the Dai Noi Hue area, which was the coronation place of the Dynasty. This is considered the center of the imperial city, also the center of the country, a symbol of the power of the Nguyen Dynasty. The palace, along with the court, was used for important imperial court ceremonies.<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/06/KPH_Tho-van-tren-kien-truc-cung-dinh-hue_DienThaiHoa.jpg"></a></p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>3. Duyệt Thị hall</strong></h3>



<p>Duyet Thi&nbsp;hall&nbsp;is located inside the Forbidden City, is a theater for the royal family to enjoy traditional music and play performance. This could be considered as the oldest theater in the Vietnam theater industry. The place has been restored and use as a theater for visitors nowadays and attracts many tourists.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>4.&nbsp;Flag tower&nbsp;– The symbol of the imperial city</strong></h3>



<p>The tower is located in the center of the south part, this is where the Dynasty hangs the royal flag. The tower is a huge architecture divided into 3 floors.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>5. Bao Vinh – The&nbsp;secret old quarter</strong></h3>



<p>This name might be a bit strange to tourists but it used to be a busy commercial place of not only the Imperial City but the whole South (also known as Đàng Trong or the Inner land).</p>



<p>The place has around 15 ancient house reserved with ancient beauty. The house owners are extremely friendly and willing to reveal interesting stories about the old days.</p>



<p>Getting a trip to Vietnam we recommend planning your trip to the airport in advance, as unexpected delays such as roadworks or poor weather can result in added stress. After you’ve booked your flights, take some time to research the best way to get to the airport within your budget. The most common options include public transport, private shuttle buses,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.flyparks.com.au/cairns-airport-parking" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">airport parking</a>, taxis, and rideshare services.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-world-heritages/the-imperial-city-of-hue-5-places-cannot-be-missed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grilled bitten-by-ants beef-an unique dish in Tam Dao</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-food-drink/grilled-bitten-by-ants-beef-an-unique-dish-in-tam-dao/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-food-drink/grilled-bitten-by-ants-beef-an-unique-dish-in-tam-dao/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:45:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam Food & Drink]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=44</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Grilled bitten-by-ants beef is a special dish served in Tam Dao, a mountainous town near Hanoi. Together with the stunning scenes, the place is home to many tasty dish and grilled bitten-by-ants beef is the most outstanding one that you should never miss in your trip to Tam Dao. The recipe to grilled beef for [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Grilled bitten-by-ants beef is a special dish served in Tam Dao, a mountainous town near Hanoi. Together with the stunning scenes, the place is home to many tasty dish and grilled bitten-by-ants beef is the most outstanding one that you should never miss in your trip to Tam Dao.</p>



<p>The recipe to grilled beef for the dish is so simple, just the same as most of the other grilled dish but the secret is about the preprocess. Fresh beef that is still warm will be hung in front of an ant net to lure the ants come for food. The ants will cut tiny pieces of the beef to bring to their net and to do this the insects have to secrete special liquid to soften the beef and the liquid is what the cook waits for as it adds flavor to the beef.<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/adb49bdcd89c31c2688d.jpg"></a></p>



<p>However, not every ant nets are chosen, local cooks only choose the nets on trees as they are clean. After deciding where to hang the fresh beef they literally poke the net so ants come out, they sense the heat and smell from fresh meet and will do a great job of preprocessing. It is said that the hotter the beef is, the more violently the ants bite and the stronger the flavor of the dish is.</p>



<p>The cook can make the dish multi-flavor by letting the beef bitten by different pieces of ants. Different pieces eat different food so the liquid they secrete has different flavor and it affects the flavor of the beef. For example, the black ants produce pungent scent, the red ants produce sour scent, other pieces produce sweetness or spice. Gourmets can tell the difference apart very well.<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/unnamed4.jpg"></a></p>



<p>After that, beef will be washed in diluted brine, dried and then grilled to medium-rare. The cook have to turn the beef over so the heat cooks it evenly. A standard grilled bitten-by-ant beef is medium-rare with the typical pink, beef is then sliced and decorated on plates ready for serving eaters.<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/Bo-Tai-Kien-Tam-Dao-3.jpg"></a></p>



<p>The beef will be served with special dipping sauce and local herbs. Eaters pick a slice of beef, roll it with herbs and dip into the vicous sauce made from corn and soy beans with sugar and juliened ginger. Herbs are usually sour star fruit, green banana and other local herbs.</p>



<p>Enjoying the dish eaters will sense an interesting flavor combined by the scents of dipping sauce, herbs, ants’ liquid. And the dish could be more than delicious when it’s enjoyed in the cold weather and fresh air of Tam Dao. Therefore, if you have opportunities to visit the foggy town on the mount, don’t forget to refresh your appetite with this unique dish.<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/ngaynaybonuonglalotmonngonvietmoiduocvinhdanh2.jpg"></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-food-drink/grilled-bitten-by-ants-beef-an-unique-dish-in-tam-dao/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to make Vietnamese pickled lemongrass chicken legs.</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-food-drink/how-to-make-vietnamese-pickled-lemongrass-chicken-legs/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-food-drink/how-to-make-vietnamese-pickled-lemongrass-chicken-legs/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam Food & Drink]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=42</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[INGREDIENTS: IMPLEMENTATION STEPS 01. Chicken feet bought and washed, cut off the nail, if the foot is still skin, peel off to clean, then soak in salt water for about 10 minutes 02. Lemongrass chopped, sliced chili and kumquat fruitwashed into slices, chopped off into slices. Peeled garlic, ginger and lime leaves into thin strips. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide size-full"><img decoding="async" src="http://localhost:8080/travelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/photo-4-1547178677563396365566.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-64"/><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Vietnamese pickled lemongrass chicken legs</figcaption></figure>



<p><strong>INGREDIENTS:</strong></p>



<ul>
<li>Chicken feet</li>



<li>Lemongrass</li>



<li>Kumquat fruit</li>



<li>Ginger</li>



<li>Garlic</li>



<li>Chili</li>



<li>Sugar, salt, fishsauce, water<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/3-cach-lam-chan-ga-sa-tac-gion-dam-vi-khong-the-cuong-lai-1.jpg"></a></li>
</ul>



<p><strong>IMPLEMENTATION STEPS</strong></p>



<p>01. Chicken feet bought and washed, cut off the nail, if the foot is still skin, peel off to clean, then soak in salt water for about 10 minutes</p>



<p>02. Lemongrass chopped, sliced chili and kumquat fruitwashed into slices, chopped off into slices. Peeled garlic, ginger and lime leaves into thin strips.</p>



<p>03. Catch boiling water for chicken feet and boil briefly. Boil water with some slices of ginger, a pinch of salt, a few branches of lemongrass to boil together to eliminate the odor of chicken feet.</p>



<p>04. After being boiled, chicken feet are put into soaked with ice soaked about 5-10px and picked out and put into box.</p>



<p>05. Make the sauce of the dish. First, boil about 1 liter of water. For boiling water, add about 6 teaspoons of sugar, 6 tablespoons of good fish sauce, 1 teaspoon of salt to stir well to dissolve the spices. Use a spoon to remove the foam so that the chicken foot bath water is clean. This fish sauce mixture will boil for about 1 minute, then turn off the heat to cool then pour into the chicken feet box. You should wait around 2 days to the chicken feet can infuse spices.<a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/photo-3-1547178677560712164792.jpg"></a></p>



<p>Are you ready to enjoy the food?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-food-drink/how-to-make-vietnamese-pickled-lemongrass-chicken-legs/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vietnam: Vinpearl Luxury Nha Trang On The World’s Top Luxury Resorts</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/top-hotels/vietnam-vinpearl-luxury-nha-trang-on-the-worlds-top-luxury-resorts/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/top-hotels/vietnam-vinpearl-luxury-nha-trang-on-the-worlds-top-luxury-resorts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Top hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=40</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Resort Vinpearl Nha Trang is listed as one of the world most wonderful resorts by Huffingtonpost. Vinpearl Luxury Nha Trang is located on the beautiful island of Hon Tre. From on yacht, you will see 84 villas spreading on white sand beach, along distant mountains. Coming to the resort, visitors will have the opportunity to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Resort Vinpearl Nha Trang is listed as one of the world most wonderful resorts by Huffingtonpost.</strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-9.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-9.jpg" alt="World-Top-Luxury-Resorts (9)" class="wp-image-1413"/></a></figure>



<p>Vinpearl Luxury Nha Trang is located on the beautiful island of Hon Tre. From on yacht, you will see 84 villas spreading on white sand beach, along distant mountains. Coming to the resort, visitors will have the opportunity to enjoy the beauty of the island and perfect care from spa services.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-1.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-1.jpg" alt="World-Top-Luxury-Resorts (1)" class="wp-image-1414"/></a></figure>



<p>Intercontinental Le Moana, at Bora, Polynesia, France is hanging on the floor of stilt houses on sea and lagoon, and owns some most beautiful bungalow resorts on water.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-2.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-2.jpg" alt="World-Top-Luxury-Resorts (2)" class="wp-image-1415"/></a></figure>



<p>Float House River Kwai, Kanchanaburi, Thailand offers visitors resorts which are designed to float on the river Khwae Noi.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-3.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-3.jpg" alt="World-Top-Luxury-Resorts (3)" class="wp-image-1416"/></a></figure>



<p>Conrad Maldives Rangali Island, Alifu Dhaalu Atoll, Maldives is located on two separate islands, visitors come here by boat only. Conrad Rangali owns more than 150 luxury villas, to meet all tastes of tourists.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-4.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-4.jpg" alt="World-Top-Luxury-Resorts (4)" class="wp-image-1419"/></a></figure>



<p>Likuliku Lagoon Resort, Mamanuca Archipelago, Fiji is located in an area with stunning views, near Nadi. The resort is designed in traditional Fijian architecture and using local materials.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-5.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-5.jpg" alt="World-Top-Luxury-Resorts (5)" class="wp-image-1418"/></a></figure>



<p>Punta Caracol Acqua Lodge – Bocas del Toro, Panama. The land of Bocas del Toro is originally famous for its colorful nightlife, beautiful parks, and beaches and is one of the popular attractions for backpacking tourists.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-6.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-6.jpg" alt="World-Top-Luxury-Resorts (6)" class="wp-image-1417"/></a></figure>



<p>Berjaya Langkawi Resort, Langkawi, Malaysia. Langkawi is an archipelago of 99 islands and is known as the “Jewel of Kedah state”.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-7.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-7.jpg" alt="World-Top-Luxury-Resorts (7)" class="wp-image-1420"/></a></figure>



<p>Song Saa Private Island, Koh Rong, Cambodia is spreading over two pristine islands, called the Song Saa. The resort is full of charm and elegance.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-8.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/World-Top-Luxury-Resorts-8.jpg" alt="World-Top-Luxury-Resorts (8)" class="wp-image-1421"/></a></figure>



<p>Constance Le Prince Maurice, Poste de Lacq, Mauritius.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/top-hotels/vietnam-vinpearl-luxury-nha-trang-on-the-worlds-top-luxury-resorts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vietnamese resorts named in world best 50 resorts 2018</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/top-hotels/vietnamese-resorts-named-in-world-best-50-resorts-2018/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/top-hotels/vietnamese-resorts-named-in-world-best-50-resorts-2018/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Top hotels]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=37</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Two Vietnamese resorts, InterContinental Danang Sun Peninsula Resort and JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay Resort &#38; Spa, have been honoured on the list of 50 best resorts in the world in 2018 as announced by the US-based luxury and lifestyle travel magazine, Condé Nast Traveler. The list was revealed based on the results of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Two Vietnamese resorts, InterContinental Danang Sun Peninsula Resort and JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay Resort &amp; Spa, have been honoured on the list of 50 best resorts in the world in 2018 as announced by the US-based luxury and lifestyle travel magazine, Condé Nast Traveler.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Danang-InterContinental-1.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Danang-InterContinental-1.jpg" alt="Danang InterContinental 1" class="wp-image-2528"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>InterContinental Danang Sun Peninsula Resort on the Son Tra Peninsula</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The list was revealed based on the results of the magazine’s Readers’ Choice Awards, including reviews of 429,000 readers.</p>



<p>InterContinental Danang Sun Peninsula Resort in Da Nang ranked 15th on the list and is described as “the perfect pick for some beachside R&amp;R while in Vietnam”.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Danang-InterContinental.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Danang-InterContinental.jpg" alt="Danang InterContinental" class="wp-image-2527"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>InterContinental Danang Sun Peninsula Resort</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>It also feels much farther away from the “real world” though it is just 30 minutes from the Danang airport, the magazine states. The resort, which opened in 2012, is said to be scattered from the lush hills of the Son Tra Peninsula nature reserve down to the sandy shores of the East Sea and has become one of the top picks in the country for relaxing getaways.</p>



<p>JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay Resort &amp; Spa, with the hotel’s 244 rooms and villas with sea views and private pools, is ranked 17th on the list.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide"><a href="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Marriott-Phu-Quoc.jpg"><img decoding="async" src="http://vietnam-online.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/10/Marriott-Phu-Quoc.jpg" alt="Marriott Phu Quoc" class="wp-image-2526"/></a><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay Resort &amp; Spa</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The hotel is designed by inimitable hotel designer Bill Bensley with the concept weaving a story around the fictional historic Lamarck University, an homage to the French evolutionary theorist, which was supposedly founded in 1880, then abandoned in the 1940s, and ultimately restored by Marriott, the magazine said.</p>



<p>Although the resort has only been in operation since late 2016, it has continuously been honoured with many prestigious world travel awards.</p>



<p><em>Source: nhandan</em></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/top-hotels/vietnamese-resorts-named-in-world-best-50-resorts-2018/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Da Lat, the city where time slows down</title>
		<link>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/da-lat-the-city-where-time-slows-down/</link>
					<comments>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/da-lat-the-city-where-time-slows-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[caotrang]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Vietnam Overview]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/?p=22</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Belonging to Lam Dong, a province of Central Highland of Vietnam, Da Lat is a small city at the altitude of 1500 meters which grants the city lovely climate that not many places in Vietnam have. With many beautiful landscapes and nice weather, Da Lat makes its way to the top destination in Vietnam and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Belonging to Lam Dong, a province of Central Highland of Vietnam, Da Lat is a small city at the altitude of 1500 meters which grants the city lovely climate that not many places in Vietnam have.</p>



<p>With many beautiful landscapes and nice weather, Da Lat makes its way to the top destination in Vietnam and its journey to higher rank in the list seems not to stop.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide size-full"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" width="700" height="400" src="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/con-duong-da-lat-a4.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-26" srcset="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/con-duong-da-lat-a4.jpg 700w, https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/con-duong-da-lat-a4-300x171.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Da Lat the foggy city</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>Thanks to its natural advantages, Da Lat is home to thousands of flower pieces, which make the city literally sank in the flower colors all year round and also the reason the city is dubbed as the city of thousands flowers, the love city or the foggy city. Granted with lovely weather that is lightly cold at night and foggy in the early morning, pine forests hugging the city, Da Lat looks definitely romantic and poetic. An as a beloved child of the God, this place has zero storm, only strong winds can reach it.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide size-full"><img decoding="async" width="700" height="500" src="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/1554722331_du-lich-da-lat-ngam-hoa-3.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-27" srcset="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/1554722331_du-lich-da-lat-ngam-hoa-3.jpg 700w, https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/1554722331_du-lich-da-lat-ngam-hoa-3-300x214.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>The stunning road of cherry blossom in Da Lat</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The first special thing that tourists to Da Lat may notice is that the city has no traffic light. It does make sense if we take a look at the geographic conditions of the city. It’s located on a plateau with many slopes so no one here ever wants to drive fast. Also, the population density in Da Lat is not high so the number of vehicles is low, roads here are quite open.&nbsp;Secondly visitors also may notice is that it’s hard to find an AC here in Da Lat and it’s totally easy to understand as it is cool all year round.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image alignwide size-full"><img decoding="async" width="1000" height="667" src="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/phuong-tim-11.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-35" srcset="https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/phuong-tim-11.jpg 1000w, https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/phuong-tim-11-300x200.jpg 300w, https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/phuong-tim-11-768x512.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption"><em>Da Lat can lack anything but flowers</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>Beside, the most obvious thing that could be sensed here in Da Lat is the peace. Unlike other cities in Vietnam, this city preserves its peaceful atmosphere quite well so visitors hardly could find a hustle and bustle city here but a dreamy city in quiet. The life beat here is quite slow, it could even affect visitors. Walking slowly in the foliage of the flower city, you may suddenly find yourself&nbsp;live, think more slowly when you’re out there in the world, even your heart beats more slowly.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://caotrang1009.github.io/webtravelnews/vietnam-overview/da-lat-the-city-where-time-slows-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
